现在，快速移动话题。
Now, moving subjects rapidly.
让我们谈谈渲染。
Let's talk about rendering.
我怎么能在 DOM里平顺点
How would I render something
smoothly in a DOM?
让我们假设我给你一个密码挑战
Let's say I give you a code challenge and
它从左到右移动了五百个像素
it's move some elements from
left to right by 500 pixels.
你怎么做到的
How would you do that?
我们，我们有甚么特性呢 ?
What we, what sort of properties
do we have in elements?
我们有位置
We have positions.
所以，在 CSS 里，你是怎么移动的，你怎么会动一个元素呢 ?
So, okay in CSS how would you move,
how would you move an element?
你在某种程度上是这样做的
It's really you've done
that at some point.
>> 页边距，页边距不同
&gt;&gt; Margins, margins are the different
对齐位置 >> I 均值，
aligning positions
&gt;&gt; I mean,
那不是，你动不了，你就不想动了
that's not, you would move the element but
you wouldn't want to move with
因为它们偏离了整个页面的布局
margins because they're off
the layout of the whole page.
您将使用位置， x 位置和 y 位置。
You would use position,
x position, y position.
x 向左， >> 左上角，
x left,
&gt;&gt; top left,
>> 左上角，右下角。
&gt;&gt; top left, bottom right.
> > 我，在这种情况下，我们会给你一个提示。
&gt;&gt; I and in this case we would
use on giving you a hint.
你怎么翻译因为翻译不像别的什么叫
How do you translate because translate,
unlike the calling anything else,
它不会强制回流。
it will not force a reflow.
它本质上是从 DOM 的流中获取的
It essentially takes it out of
the the flow of the DOM and
它就会独立移动
it just moves it independently.
你们都在 CSS里做过这个
And you've all done this in CSS.
但当你坐在白板上
But when you're sitting on a whiteboard,
要记住这些事情就更难了
it's much harder to
remember all these things.
>> 但是知道，渲染和理解，好吧，
&gt;&gt; But knowing, rendering and
understanding, okay,
我们理解并采取行动
we understand and move position.
我们都是在 CSS里做的
We do it all the time in CSS.
执行 JavaScript 只是手动调用此样式。
Doing JavaScript is just doing
calling this styles manually.
所以有些元素是那种风格变换
So some element that style, transform,
转换 x，和我们在 JavaScript中做的 CSS 一样。
translate x, the same thing doing
CSS we're just doing in JavaScript.
但我们如何才能让事情进展顺利呢 ?
But how do we get
something to move smoothly?
这是一个很好的问题。
This is a good actually
high level question.
你怎么能平顺点
How would you smoothly animate something?
>> CSS 转换。
&gt;&gt; CSS transitions.
> > 不错，嗯。
&gt;&gt; It's not bad, yeah.
但如果我们在 JAVA 脚本中这样做，我们正在使用请求动画框架。
But if we're doing it in JAVA script,
we're using request animation frame.
现在是什么请求动画框架?
Now what is request animation frame?
你听说过吗
Have you heard of it?
好吧好吧
All right.
因此，请求动画框架是窗口对象上的全局可用功能。
So request animation frame is a globally
available function on the Window objects.
每次都有渲染的结果
And what it does is every
time there's a render,
它会调用 requestAnimationFrame。
it makes a call to requestAnimationFrame.
这很重要因为如果我们想要得到流畅的动画
And this is important because if we're
trying to get a smooth animation,
我们不想要任何的眩晕
we don't want any stuttering.
这意味着每次都有新的渲染我们要移动它
That means every time there's
a new render, we wanna move it
再多一点，我们就想把那个元素再移一点。
just a little bit more, we wanna move
that element just a little bit more.
所有浏览器都呈现每秒 60 帧的情况
And all browsers render that 60 frames
a second That means in one second it's
将请求 requestAnimationFrame 近似秒。
gonna call requestAnimationFrame
approximately seconds.
只有当情况发生时才会顺利的
Station frame it's gonna smoothly
only when the render happens.
如果你要做一些短小的游戏就永远不可能
It'll never block if you're
making some short game or
狂妄的使用 requestAnimationFrame ，如果您不知道它，
arrogant use requestAnimationFrame
If you didn't know about it,
这是在 JavaScript中进行计时的另一种方式，
it is another way of doing
timing in JavaScript,
如果你想要每 16 毫秒发生一件事
if you wanted something to happen
every 16 or so milliseconds, roughly.
有一些边缘案例，但我不想太过分。
There are edge cases, but
I don't wanna go too far into that.
所以知道每 16 毫秒
So knowing that every 16
something milliseconds
调用请求动画帧。
request animation frame is called.
这就是我们要做所有动画的地方
That's where we wanna do all for
animations.
解决下一个问题。
Suite our next problem.
这正是我所描述的
It's exactly what I described.
我要你移动一个元素我给你一个真正的面试
I want you to move an elements and
I gave you a hint in a real interview,
他们不会告诉你使用请求动画框架
they wouldn't tell you to
use request Animation Frame.
我们来看看这个。
Let's take a look at this one.
用于移动元素的创意函数 >> 参数为持续时间。
Creative function to move an element
&gt;&gt; The arguments are the duration.
所以如果我要移动 500 像素，超过 10 秒，
So if I want to move 500 pixels,
over 10 seconds,
我在一万毫秒或几秒内过去并不重要。
I pass in 10,000 milliseconds or
seconds doesn't really matter.
我得说像素是 500
I'd say the pixel so that'd be 500.
然后我就把这些元素放进去了
And then I put in the elements and move.
你可以在 CSS里做这个
You could do this in CSS.
如果您希望这样做，那么这是数据条的良好应用。
If you want it to But
this is a good application of data strips.
这是个小数学
It's a little math heavy.
但这要取决于你的态度
But this have to be,
it depends on your approach.